<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<REVIEWS>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>1</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Staff</Name>
    <SDate>1900-01-01T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>1900-01-01T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight>Rodnaya is impressively stylish yet it’s also warmly welcoming to families with its great range of facilities and safety features.&nbsp; We regret not bringing our kids along for this visit, as they would have loved the children’s play room after an afternoon in the pool.&nbsp; We also love gorgeous, peaceful Nai Thon Beach, which is somehow still overlooked by most visitors to Phuket.</RHighlight>
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>P00154</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>With spectacular views over an idyllic white-sand beach and lush tropical parkland, a contemporary, uplifting design, a private pool that reaches out to the sky, a dedicated team of staff, delicious meals prepared by the chef and facilities catering to families, the beautiful Rodnaya is what we’d call a Goldilocks villa: it blends stylish, fun and accessible features – and an enchanting location – to create a holiday home that’s just right for all. &nbsp; We loved the full range of experiences to enjoy within a day at Rodnaya, from unwinding in five-star comfort and service to exploring the natural beauty of an unspoilt tropical beach just beyond our doorstep.&nbsp; We had an early-morning swim in the pool, then a decadent breakfast on the terrace.&nbsp; Later on, we took a stroll along the sand and munched on grilled chicken on a skewer from a beachside food vendor.&nbsp; Then back up to the villa in time for sunset cocktails and an elaborate dinner of rich Thai curries, spicy fish and stir-fried veggies, all planned the day before with our chef.&nbsp; Finally to bed, where the master suite offers a soft, sumptuous embrace and the promise of more fabulous sea views, just a curtain-peek away upon waking up tomorrow. </ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise>The beach is in full view but it’s a steep walk to get there!&nbsp; Don’t worry though, lifts there and back can be easily arranged with the villa manager.&nbsp; With its beautiful design and awesome views, it’s a shame that events are not permitted at Rodnaya, but guests looking for an event venue could try Villa Haleana , also within the Malaiwana estate.</RUnpleasantSurprise>
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>8.70</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>9</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>9</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>8</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>9</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>8</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>8</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>9</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>9</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>9</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>9</RIValue>
    <RIDate>1900-01-01T00:00:00+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Staff</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>1</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID21783009</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Cho Yee Bonnie Wong</Name>
    <SDate>2018-04-27T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2018-04-30T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>P00154</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>This is the best villa in Phuket. The villa is sttuning. The service team members are helpful. It’s the best choice for family, friend gathering place. The chef is very accommodating and food quality is good. The home is kept so tidy and clean. Good attitude of service is highly appreciated.
I recommend this villa with no hesitation only the location is a bit out from the Phuket Town so if you are looking for shopping you may need to spend 30-45 mins to get there for shops. Otherwise it’s one of the best choices to stay in Phuket. 

</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2018-05-21T10:43:41.913+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Cho Yee Bonnie W, Hong Kong</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID21783008</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID22157339</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Sense Luxury Sense Luxury</Name>
    <SDate>2018-08-20T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2018-08-24T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>P00154</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>Good service. We stay here very happy. Katy works very nice.</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2018-08-25T00:00:00+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Yujia F, China</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID22157338</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID22315663</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Jack Dai</Name>
    <SDate>2018-10-17T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2018-10-21T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>P00154</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>A beautiful villa with a splendid view. The staff are great. They are very lovely and make this trip ever so much better. The food is another highlight. We have had so much fun and will miss this villa alot.</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2018-11-29T15:11:39.34+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Jacqueline D, Hong Kong</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID22315662</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
</REVIEWS>