<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<REVIEWS>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>1</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Staff</Name>
    <RHighlight>The staff were certainly one of the highlights for us.&nbsp; The villa manager takes great care in making sure the villa runs like clockwork and that guests feel looked after at all times.&nbsp; The location is wonderful too – close the beach and the excellent restaurants, shops and beach bars in and around Berawa.&nbsp; We also loved the large guest kitchen, which is perfect if you want to do some cooking yourself – not to mention the espresso machine.<br /></RHighlight>
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>P00225</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>Villa Indrani’s exterior blends in perfectly with its surroundings, but once we stepped into the monumental entrance hall we were blown away by its sheer size and chic design<br /><br />The villa has a stylish and neutral interior with authentic Balinese paintings and antiques adding a subtle shot of local character, while nonetheless staying true to its overall minimalist theme. <br /><br />The open-plan, ground floor living and dining room space was my personal favourite.&nbsp; The modern kitchen and large comfortable sofas make this a great area for hanging out and entertaining.&nbsp; As a wannabe barista I was particularly taken in by the Simonelli espresso machine – this really is the Rolls Royce of coffee makers.&nbsp; Simply ask one of the helpful butlers to make you a cuppa, sit back and experience the taste of coffee the way it was always intended to taste. <br /><br />Speaking of butlers, we were really impressed by the professionalism and friendliness of the staff throughout our stay. I’d particularly single out the chef who was more than happy to adapt to my partner’s vegan preferences, and villa manager, Made, who gave us some excellent insights into local Balinese culture.&nbsp; We even had the privilege of attending a small Balinese ceremony at the villa’s little shrine – a really unique ‘Bali experience’. <br /><br />The outdoor areas are great for lounging in the sun or cooling off in the 10-metre pool.&nbsp; Indrani’s courtyard garden is perhaps a little small given the size of the villa, but that didn’t really matter given how much time we spent on the beach.&nbsp; Most of the rooms overlook the pool and garden, which is ideal if you have young children to keep an eye on. <br /><br />We really enjoyed Indrani’s location so close to the beach.&nbsp; It’s also great for exploring the rest of Bali – especially as it’s an easy drive towards the glamour of Seminyak or the hipster vibes of Batu Bolong and Canggu.<br /></ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise>The pool and garden may have been relatively small compared to the rest of the villa, but its great beach-side location definitely made up for that.&nbsp; There’s a large accessible roof which has awesome views and which would make a lovely rooftop terrace, but at the moment it is simply pebbled and there’s no seating available.&nbsp; There was some sound from the security post travelling into the upstairs master bedroom, but this was quickly resolved once we informed the villa manager.<br /></RUnpleasantSurprise>
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>8.30</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>8</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>9</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>7</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>9</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>9</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>8</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>8</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>8</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>9</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>8</RIValue>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Staff</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>1</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
</REVIEWS>