<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<REVIEWS>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>1</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Staff</Name>
    <SDate>2011-08-25T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2011-08-25T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight><p>
	Sleeping in the antique ceremonial beds in the fabulous main house master bedroom was the closest I&rsquo;ll ever get to royalty. A wonderful tribute to traditional craftsmanship, this room truly is fit for a king or queen, while its huge terrace with antique daybeds and (much-used) hammock made a glorious spot for afternoon tea and siestas. The typically Balinese gardens were some of the prettiest I&rsquo;ve ever encountered &ndash; especially when lantern-lit at night.</p>
</RHighlight>
    <RSurroundArea><p>
	With its vast expanse of broad golden sands sheltered by a reef, Sanur is more protected than Bali&rsquo;s western beaches, so the sea is calmer and safe for swimming &ndash; ideal for youngsters &ndash; and there&rsquo;s a huge variety of water sports available. Surfers can take a boat out to the reef from November to April, which produces lovely long hollow waves at high tides, while nearby islands Nusa Penida and Nusa Lembongan offer great dive sites and rich marine life. I think Sanur&rsquo;s best feature, however, is the promenade running the entire five-kilometre length of the beach, providing leisurely evening strolls and several stops for beachside eats, drinks and shopping!</p>
</RSurroundArea>
    <VillaID>TamanSorga</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments><p>
	On arrival at Taman Sorga, I was astounded by the villa&rsquo;s size, sheer grandeur and gorgeous traditional touches. It&rsquo;s obvious that this private and much-loved residence has been designed essentially to host a large family in the height of comfort, and to balance everyone&rsquo;s needs &ndash; from grandparents to babies.<br />
	With an emphasis on quiet villa life (events, parties and boisterous behavior are not encouraged here), there really is something for everyone. Children can stay happily amused for hours messing about in the pool, watching DVDs on one of numerous TVs, or losing themselves in the vast gardens which are perfect for hide and seek. The dining room veranda with low level table and floor cushions provides a great spot for children to indulge in adult-free meals.<br />
	<br />
	And while the twin rooms in the guest wing are just made for children, and the downstairs master bedroom is equally ideal for older guests &ndash; others might appreciate the romance and ambiance of the two eclectically furnished bedrooms in the main house.<br />
	<br />
	If you do feel the need for diversion further afield, the beach is just a short stroll down the road. Chef Wayan kindly showed me the way there, but it&rsquo;s easy to find and great for early morning dips. Sanur remains a mellow destination with a village atmosphere that&rsquo;s ideal for those who don&rsquo;t want the hustle and bustle of the south-west coast but still seek enough activity to keep them entertained during the holiday.</p>
</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise><p>
	There&rsquo;s a resident (adorable) family dog, but he can be banished to staff quarters during your stay if preferred. All rooms face inwards so don&rsquo;t expect magnificent views from your porch &ndash; although the gardens, pool and coconut palms are very picturesque! Within the grounds there are numerous streams, pools and fountains, so very young children will need to be supervised. Parents may also want to restricted children&rsquo;s activities in some parts of the villa, given the antique furnishings and d&eacute;cor.</p>
</RUnpleasantSurprise>
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>8.80</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>10</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>8</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>9</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>9</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>10</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>9</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>8</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>8</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>8</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>9</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2011-08-25T00:00:00+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Staff</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>1</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID10631251</ReviewsID>
    <Name>private leasure  international</Name>
    <SDate>2012-04-08T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2012-04-14T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>TamanSorga</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>Excellent villa.  Great staff. will recommend.</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>8.60</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>9</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>5</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>8</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>9</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>9</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>9</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>9</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>9</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>10</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>9</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2012-05-04T14:52:08.247+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>WG</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID10631250</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID14833471</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Floora de Wit</Name>
    <SDate>2013-03-28T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2013-04-03T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>TamanSorga</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>I have been to paradise on earth! The villa was absolutely amazing and so relaxing. It offered everything we could possibly want or need.
The staff were very accomodating and were an absolute delight to get to know. They took care of all our needs completely and made our time at the villa even more special.</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>9.80</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>10</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>8</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>10</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>10</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>10</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>10</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>10</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>10</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>10</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>10</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2013-04-15T10:38:29.303+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>DF, Australia</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID14833470</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID15268437</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Nathan Bigelow</Name>
    <SDate>2013-05-07T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2013-05-13T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>TamanSorga</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>Great place! The staff and accommodations were both amazing. I'd love to go back.</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>9.50</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>10</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>7</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>10</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>10</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>10</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>10</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>10</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>10</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>10</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>8</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2013-05-21T11:37:30.437+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Nathan B, United States</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID15268436</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID5276004</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Henrik Sleimann Petersen</Name>
    <SDate>2011-07-16T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2011-07-30T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight xml:space="preserve">  </RHighlight>
    <RSurroundArea xml:space="preserve">    </RSurroundArea>
    <VillaID>TamanSorga</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>My family and I spend 2 weeks at Villa Taman Sorga in july 2011. It was a great vacation and the villa comes with our highest recommendation for others to try.
The quality of the villa is at the top of the line, the staff extremely friendly and will all go out of their way to make your stay memorable and second to none. Our teenage daughter found the the Villa a bit too far from nightlife, but for the rest of our group (aged 3 to 68 years old) it was absolutely perfect.
Henrik Sleimann Petersen - Denmark</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise xml:space="preserve">  </RUnpleasantSurprise>
    <RRestShop xml:space="preserve">  </RRestShop>
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>9.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>9</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>5</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>9</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>10</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>10</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>10</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>10</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>8</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>10</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>9</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2011-08-08T15:15:47.107+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Henrik Sleimann Petersen, Denmark</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID5276003</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID6198170</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Brian Tasker</Name>
    <SDate>2011-10-29T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2011-11-05T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>TamanSorga</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>Villa Taman Sorga is a great value for money villa. although the sweimming pool is a little small, the landscaped grounds are unsurpassed after 4 visits to Bali. It creates a terrific haven from a fairly dirty and undeveloped end of Sanur.
Staff were most helpful and professional. They were accommodating and flexible and were a very big reaons wny we would rate our stay for a week here as one of the best experiences we have had in Bali</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>8.80</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>9</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>6</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>10</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>10</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>9</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>9</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>9</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>8</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>8</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>10</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2011-11-18T14:26:11.913+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Brian Tasker, Australia</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID6198169</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID6329069</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Cheryl Pongrac</Name>
    <SDate>2011-11-05T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2011-11-12T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>TamanSorga</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>To who it may concern, we stayed at Taman Sorga from the 05/12/11 for 7 nights and we loved the place. the staff were fantastic and couldnt do enough for us. We arranged for the chef to cook all our breakfast for the week and we had 2 dinners as well with that much food left over for 2 lunches. the rooms were beautiful as were the grounds. The staff do a wonderful job and made us feel like it was our own home. Any time we needed anything from the super market, [bintang] George was on it straight away. I would love to stayed there again  and i would recomend to my friends as would all of the others that stayed with me., thank you Tina from marketing villas ltd for being there for me when i booked and helping me with everything and once again thank you to the staff at Taman Sorga, you were great.</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>9.40</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>10</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>7</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>7</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>10</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>10</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>10</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>10</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>10</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>10</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>10</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2011-11-25T13:37:04.34+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Cheryl Pongrac, Australia</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID6329068</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
</REVIEWS>