<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<REVIEWS>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>1</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Staff</Name>
    <SDate>2014-01-16T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2014-01-16T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight><p>Almost every aspect of Ban Suriya is a highlight.&nbsp; The bathrooms are certainly worth a special mention thanks to the semi-outdoor designs and indoor landscaping, as are the multifarious, attractively furnished lounge areas (four in all, if you count the one in master suite). The gym annex is a ‘villa within a villa’ and a great option for older kids or singles. Outside, the poolside<span style="font-style: italic;"> sala</span> is an appealing place for drinks and dinner and the tree house is a stroke of genius that will delight kids and adults alike.</p></RHighlight>
    <RSurroundArea><p>
	There&#39;s really very little to pull you away from the facilities and comforts at Ban Suriya. A stroll along the sand provides a sense of the island&#39;s past and the local fishermen and coconut farmers generally go about their business as if you weren&#39;t there.<br />
	<br />
	For a slight variation, a day spent poolside at Nikki Beach, just ten minutes&rsquo; walk away, sipping mojitos and snacking on haute cuisine while listening to the latest dance tunes spun by the resident DJ, makes a nice change (although you can do all that onsite at Ban Suriya). Sunsets from Lipa Noi are some of the best on the island so you can time your indulgences to match the backdrop.<br />
	<br />
	Further afield, the evening food market by the main ferry pier in Nathon offers a buzzing local scene and a sharp but interesting contrast to the island&#39;s more sophisticated side. Lamai (15km) is Samui&#39;s second largest tourist beach and offers all the benefits of an international tourist town with a choice of supermarkets, shops, restaurants and nightlife. But it&#39;s only worth a visit if you crave busier, more commercial surroundings.</p>
</RSurroundArea>
    <VillaID>Suriya</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments><p>Ban Suriya is one of those villas where, as reviewers, you find yourself looking for something negative just to tick the ‘Surprises’ box. We failed.<br /><br />Our time passed far too quickly at Ban Suriya.&nbsp; In fact, a month would probably be needed to enjoy the villa to the full. It's not only the salubrious surroundings that stand out, it's the way everything seems to go that extra mile to please.&nbsp; There's not just a computer, there's an iMac packed with tunes that you can play through Bose speakers in the lounge and poolside <span style="font-style: italic;">sala</span> (gazebo).&nbsp; The gym is not only well-equipped, it has a fridge, and a plunge pool bigger than some other villas' main pool.&nbsp; Even the DVD collection includes films you wish you'd remembered to buy at the airport.<br /><br />Ironically, even with so many options we found ourselves drawn to the simplest – the tree house by the beach. The staff is clearly proud to be part of the Ban Suriya experience and the live-in manager was knowledgeable and keen to help us appreciate the villa's pleasures. Although each bedroom is noticeably different, with no one losing out, the master is clearly the most extravagant with its terrazzo bath tub and ensuite lounge. Clever design touches in the guest rooms like direct pool and jacuzzi access, indulgent semi-outdoor bathrooms and hand-picked, stylish furnishings ensure everyone is content, while those staying the twin bedroom by the games room and gym or cosseted in the beachfront pavilion also enjoy complete privacy and independence.<br /><br />Eight people is probably the minimum number you would need to fully appreciate this villa (there's an option to rent four bedrooms outside peak season), otherwise you might struggle to appreciate its exuberance.</p></ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise><p>We found only pleasant surprises, really.&nbsp; Occasional traffic noise from the road behind the villa may worry sensitive souls, but it's only noticeable because the location is so serene.&nbsp; Although Ban Suriya is definitely family-friendly, the ‘floating’ stairs leading to the mezzanine lounge, the sliding doors opening directly to the pool, and the ungated beach access mean it would be wise to keep small children closely supervised.</p></RUnpleasantSurprise>
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>9.20</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>9</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>9</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>10</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>9</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>9</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>9</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>9</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>10</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>9</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>9</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2014-01-16T00:00:00+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Staff</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>1</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID21574156</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Acquired bookings Acquired bookings</Name>
    <SDate>2018-02-13T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2018-02-18T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>Suriya</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>We love your place. A wonderful home and facilities. Yours staff are very professional and very nice. Please thanks them for us. And we hope to come back soon. Thank you for your kindness. Please don't forget my recipe of the spaghetti!!</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2018-02-23T14:10:08.073+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Ons Sidi A, Philippines</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID21574155</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID21632529</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Nomad The Luxe agent</Name>
    <SDate>2018-03-01T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2018-03-08T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>Suriya</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>Can't believe how time just flies in Ban Suriya. The Villa is amazing but what makes it more special is the crew! They are warm and inviting and they treat us like family. They absolutely adore our twins and in return, all of us had a fantastic time. Their attentiveness to all of our requests is incredible. Two thumbs up for the delicious food! We will definitely miss this villa and the most kind and gracious crew, We don't want to go back home. All the best Ban Suriya, keep being special!



</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2018-05-12T12:15:32.25+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Jon P, Singapore</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID21632528</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID21657555</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Acquired bookings Acquired bookings</Name>
    <SDate>2018-03-12T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2018-03-17T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>Suriya</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>Thanks to Tik and the amazing team. The most magnificent location on the planet crowned the most magnificent wedding! Five days of bliss made splendidly effortless by a great team. Thanks for your warm hospitality, excellent cooking - Pueng was Fantastic! Can't wait to come back. 
</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2018-05-12T12:16:52.31+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Heather L, Philippines</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID21657554</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID21694058</ReviewsID>
    <Name> EIHAB TRAVELS LLC</Name>
    <SDate>2018-03-24T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2018-03-29T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>Suriya</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>Thank you sooo much for making this holiday a fantastic one. Tik, Kai, Mohammed and everyone else that has worked so hard this week to make our stay unforgettable. We loved everything here - from the food, service, property to the friendly security guard that made us feel very safe while sleeping through the night. This place is definitely one of our favorites and you will see us again. Thank you for all the mangoes! </ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2018-05-12T12:17:55.11+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Arun A, Oman</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID21694057</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID3694344</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Adrian Lim</Name>
    <SDate>2010-11-10T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2010-11-14T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight xml:space="preserve">  </RHighlight>
    <RSurroundArea xml:space="preserve">    </RSurroundArea>
    <VillaID>Suriya</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>Ban Suriya is indeed great! We all had fun as guests and we were never bored. The staff on board were all very accommodating. Truely impressed!</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise xml:space="preserve">  </RUnpleasantSurprise>
    <RRestShop xml:space="preserve">  </RRestShop>
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>8.20</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>8</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>8</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>9</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>8</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>7</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>8</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>7</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>9</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>10</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>8</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2010-12-01T16:45:26.903+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Adrian Lim </ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID3694343</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID21712035</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Acquired bookings Acquired bookings</Name>
    <SDate>2018-03-30T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2018-04-05T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>Suriya</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>It was so wonderful to come back to this beautiful place again. You Tik and your fabulous team made our holiday for us and our friends really special and unforgettable - especially your marvelous Thai cuisine (yummy yummy). Your warm hospitality and your lovely decorations made our holiday extraordinary, thank you so much!
</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2018-05-12T12:20:04.533+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Niewodniczanski P, Germany</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID21712034</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
</REVIEWS>