<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<REVIEWS>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>1</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Staff</Name>
    <SDate>2013-04-16T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2013-04-16T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight><p>
	When you have a stunning white beach and turquoise water it is difficult to really pick out anything else. What is nice though is how the villa has maximised the experience &ndash; it can be enjoyed over mealtimes, playtime and down time. The staff can make or break a villa vacation &ndash; in this case it is a definite make. Khun Joy is literally a real Joy. Her happy outlook and continuous willingness to help made our stay perfect. Be careful though she bakes a wicked chocolate cake!</p>
</RHighlight>
    <RSurroundArea><p>
	There is really little need to know what is in the surrounding area because it is highly unlikely you will want to leave the villa, most guests do not. That said, there is actually very little. The local restaurants near the pier about a kilometre up the beach are not worth the effort. There is an ATM here though if you need money to settle bills. Adjacent to Waimarie are three or four more magnificent villas which will often mean kids find new friends to explore with. Beyond the villas is a larger unfinished development &ndash; The Place, which is sufficiently far away not to disturb. The other side of the development is a small fishing village. If you do want to explore you will need a car. Khun Joy can arrange car hire and taxis.</p>
</RSurroundArea>
    <VillaID>Waimarie</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments><p>
	Waimarie is one of the most homely villas we have inspected. It&rsquo;s incredibly well thought out for families, with absolutely loads to do even on a rainy day (heaven forbid). What really struck us as sensible is that all the day-time lounging areas make the most of the beach and views, whilst the bedrooms are set behind in lovely mature gardens which provide more privacy. The bedrooms are so practical for families &ndash; connecting rooms, twin with kings, but each still having a huge bathroom. Perhaps the connecting door could be a bit more sound-proofed.<br />
	<br />
	The baths are huge enough to take five or six kids (or two adults) with ease. Use the shower every other day to appease your environmentally-aware conscience. The common areas are excellent &ndash; a little well used in places but not in a frustrating way. There are loads of places to curl up in with a good book but also keep an eye on proceedings. Home away from home is a much overused term but we think this is very applicable for Waimarie. Warm, friendly, secure and incredibly homely.</p>
</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise><p>
	The staff at the villa are delightful and incredibly helpful but only the charming Khun Joy speaks fluent English so direct your requests through her. This is generally not an issue as Joy is ever present and takes great pride ensuring that guests enjoy their Waimarie experience. Joy will also arrange any outside activities, transport etc. Some guest may be disappointed that there are no TVs or stereos in the bedrooms but we spent so much time around the pool it hardly seemed an issue.</p>
</RUnpleasantSurprise>
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>8.40</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>9</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>9</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>9</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>9</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>8</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>8</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>7</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>9</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>9</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>7</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2013-04-16T00:00:00+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Staff</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>1</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID21572471</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Acquired bookings Acquired bookings</Name>
    <SDate>2018-01-27T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2018-02-17T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>Waimarie</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>Thank you so much to Joy and the team at Waimarie for a wonderful, relaxing, delicious 3 weeks. Joy's hospitality and creativity (with lots of special surprises) contributed to making our stay truly memorable. The food was exquisite, fresh, tasty and healthy, a great chef. Loads of tennis with James kept us in shape. We had a great time, Thanks
</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2018-04-30T16:43:33.917+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Ed A, Thailand</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID21572470</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID21617374</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Acquired bookings Acquired bookings</Name>
    <SDate>2018-02-24T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2018-03-04T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>Waimarie</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>Thank you Joy for all the good care and hospitality you have showed us. Special thanks for all your help after the dog bite...priceless. All the best 
</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2018-05-08T13:38:52.703+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Henrik W, Thailand</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID21617373</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID21679120</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Lily Chan</Name>
    <SDate>2018-03-20T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2018-03-24T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>Waimarie</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>Thank you Joy and your staff for all your loving care. Everything is just "perfect" - as always.
</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2018-05-13T16:51:59.827+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Lily C, Philippines</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID21679119</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID21717813</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Sebastian Emilian Balasescu</Name>
    <SDate>2018-03-31T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2018-04-08T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>Waimarie</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>We have spent a wonderful and relaxing week. All of this was possible because Joy and her team did their best in order for us to have an amazing holiday. Here we found a great chef who cooked everything we asked for. We wish we will come back here for a longer period of time.
</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2018-05-18T17:21:52.767+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Sebastian Emilian B, Romania</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID21717812</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID21895522</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Simon Clarke</Name>
    <SDate>2018-04-27T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2018-05-01T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>waimarie</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>Thank you for your amazing hospitality and care. Awesome food and great property. We've had a lovely time. Kids love this place! Julian and I had a wonderful time. The staff were super attentive and the property is beautiful. We thoroughly enjoyed our trip and look forward to a return down the road.</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2018-06-18T09:15:26.52+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Simon and Friends, Hong Kong</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>OPOceane</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
</REVIEWS>