<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<REVIEWS>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>1</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Staff</Name>
    <SDate>2014-11-03T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2014-11-03T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight>Where do we start?&nbsp; Villa Kaba Kaba satisfies on so many levels and offers so many things to do, see and experience that everything is a highlight.&nbsp; Be sure to take some time to enjoy the estate’s eclectic collection of artworks and antiques, which will delight seasoned art lovers and amaze a whole new generation.&nbsp; And if you are planning to tie the knot, and want to invite lots of relatives and friends. . .&nbsp; well, wedding venues don’t get much get better than this.<br /></RHighlight>
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>P00017</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>We’ve been lucky enough to visit a lot of beautiful villas in our time, but Kaba Kaba Estate exceeded all expectations of comfort, luxuriousness, good taste and space.&nbsp; There’s so much to do on the estate itself that its out-of-town location is not an issue.&nbsp; Everything has been thought of, from tennis, foosball, air hockey and all the major electronic game consoles, through to a library, gym and even a croquet lawn.&nbsp; If only we’d had more time!&nbsp; As it was, the pools, the spa and the spectacular home cinema were more than enough to relax and entertain us. <br />&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;<br />The staff were just the right mix of professional and friendly, and the chef is a consummate pro, delighting us with everything he presented.&nbsp; Although there is a selection menu, we highly suggest that you just ‘go blind’ (like we did) and let the chef and his team surprise you with their magic.&nbsp; Our simple, three-course Balinese dinner was off-the-charts delicious.<br /><br />Do go for an early morning wander through the rice fields.&nbsp; The locals are very friendly and the experience will be something the regular tour guides can’t give you.&nbsp; The wide-open spaces are awe inspiring. <br /></ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise>The villa has been meticulously designed and so well thought out that there is virtually nothing wrong with it.&nbsp; One word of warning though, because the place is so big it may not be so easy to keep a track of little ones, and the many ponds and water features around the place will no doubt draw the attention of inquisitive toddlers.<br /></RUnpleasantSurprise>
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>9.30</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>10</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>8</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>10</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>10</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>10</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>9</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>10</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>10</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>9</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>7</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2014-11-03T00:00:00+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Staff</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>1</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID19510138</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Ltd Maisonbulle</Name>
    <SDate>2015-10-28T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2015-12-14T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>P00017</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>This has been the most a magical time for us. Thank you very much for welcoming us so warmly and carrying us into your home. I can’t tell how well you have taken good care & we have felt it has simply been spectacular. The attention to detail is unrivaled. Rahmat is quite unique - completely relaxed on surface and yet an incredible manager ensuring everything all goes without mistake, quite incredible. Everyone from the security team, gardeners, engineer, housekeeping, butler, kitchen staff and secretary have been lovely, professional + fully smile + charm. We will miss you all very much. Thank you, Thank you, Thank you for making the memories. </ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2016-07-17T13:41:40.577+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Aisha A, United Kingdom</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID19510137</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID19854775</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Lokal Living Lokal Living</Name>
    <SDate>2016-05-12T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2016-05-15T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>P00017</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>We were recommended to look at Kaba Kaba Estate to celebrate my 30th birthday and recent engagement. Our guests flew from LA, UK, Hong Kong and Singapore. The entire weekend experience was more than we could here asked for. The villa is well maintained and gorgeous. But what truly made our time special was attentive and gentle natural of the staff. No request was too small or too impossible to ask for. The entire staff took the initiative at all times and made our guests feel completely at home. However, two people truly deserve special mention, the first is Kadek, who from the moment we walked in was implacably dressed and ready to attend to every our need. The second is Rahmat, without Rahmat to managing the staff, our holiday would not have resulted in such memorable weekend. Rahmat also was helping me manage a fleet of cars going back and forth between other villas. He is such joy to deal with, he is always on the ball, understands guest needs and clearly goes over and above.  </ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2016-07-17T18:01:13.677+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Liling O, Indonesia</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID19854774</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID20218569</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Bhavana Punj</Name>
    <SDate>2016-10-07T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2016-10-11T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>P00017</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>We stayed at Kaba Kaba for our family holiday from June 7th - 11 Oct 2016. We had very high expectations after all the researched we have done. And the experience has surpassed our all expectations. The staff were extremely helpful and warm. They were very patient with our children and took care of all their needs. We had an incredible time and much of it was thanks to you.The villa is beautifully designed and the rooms are spacious and every details has been taken care off.
Our experience has been fabulous and we will positively visit again soon.</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2016-12-04T16:19:31.763+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Bhavana P, India</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID20218568</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID20256257</ReviewsID>
    <Name>VM Kaba Kaba</Name>
    <SDate>2016-10-17T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2016-10-21T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>p00017</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>Thank you very much for your time and help, We are very enjoyed our stay in the villa, we will be back again.</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2016-12-04T16:20:12.933+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Christian & Yasmeen, Indonesia</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>VMKabaKaba</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID20291453</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Elmar Metry</Name>
    <SDate>2016-10-28T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2016-11-06T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>P00017</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>From the deepest bottom of our heart, we would like to thank you for this unforgettable holiday, which was soooo romantic. You made this place our "home away from home" and we are definitely want to come back, come back to the place where I proposed to my future wife! It will forever be in our heart.
Rahmat..my brother..thank you for your love and dedication! You make this place unforgettable. Sincere thanks for whole team - you're awesome.</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2016-12-04T16:22:24.823+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Elmar M, Switzerland</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID20291452</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID20416292</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Nomad The Luxe agent</Name>
    <SDate>2016-12-18T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2016-12-25T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>P00017</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>The kaba kaba estate is simply stunning luxurious living set in countryside natural surrounding. A five star property supported by world class service and support staff make your stay much more special. The attention of details every aspect of the estate is very apparent from the moment you set foot on the estate. Thank you Pak Rahmat and team for looking after us and treating us so well. Hope to return some day in the near future.</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2017-03-04T16:25:55.093+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Joey A, Malaysia</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID20416291</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID20543133</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Sense Luxury Sense Luxury</Name>
    <SDate>2017-01-30T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2017-02-04T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>P00017</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>The villa is wonderful, enjoy the stay and everything are perfect, the service is great and planning will coming back.</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2017-03-05T15:40:22.69+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Jin J, China</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID20543132</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID20727072</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Stacey Margaret Haines</Name>
    <SDate>2017-04-08T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2017-04-14T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>P00017</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>Thank you so much for such as wonderful holiday at Estate Kaba Kaba, the service provided by the staff made the 50th Birthday very special and one I will always remember, thank you. The Estate Kaba Kaba is amazing, the grounds, the design of the suites, the peaceful setting. The staff are excellent. The food fabulous, really could not find fault with anything..felt very spoilt. Such a lovely relaxing place, wonderful staff who go above and beyond to make your stay memorable. Rahmat has been incredible. </ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2017-05-14T17:31:09.773+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Stacey Margaret H, Australia</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID20727071</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID20877879</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Emma Whiting  Travel</Name>
    <SDate>2017-06-07T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2017-06-11T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>P00017</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>From the moment we arrived the staff of Kaba Kaba Estate have shown us true genuine and warm Balinese hospitality. Our group of 20 found Kaba Kaba to be an exceptional home away from home. Absolutely anything and everything that we asked for was always met with a smile, grace and a can do attitude. Kaba Kaba Estate is a stunning hidden home away from the hustle and bustle of the better known holiday resorts. It is perfect estate for those like us, who wanted to relax in beautiful and tastefully decorated luxury villa. One of our group owns and manages a hotel in Melbourne wants to take Rahmat Villa Manager home. Half of us work in travel industry, from airlines to cruise ships to managing travel agencies. We all know and understand how difficult it can be for things to seem effortless. We would like to all personally to thank Rahmat for his professionalism, relaxed approach and smile, we acknowledge his job is made easier from all the team members around him including the ones we don't see. Thank you.</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2017-07-06T00:00:23.077+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Kirk W, Australia</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID20877878</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID21023061</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Adam Partridge</Name>
    <SDate>2017-07-16T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2017-07-24T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>P00017</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>We come to Bali to celebrate the 30th Birthday of a very special family member. 9 adult and 8 children under 9 years of age. A very ambitious project but such a wise choice in selecting Kaba Kaba Estate. Rahmat and his incredible team ensure the villa was our home for 8 days. Such warm atmosphere where every staff member is attentive and yet unobtrusive. No doubt we brought a lot of noise to the estate but there is always a tranquil corner to be found in the vast home or in the magnificent gardens. It is a credit to Rahmat that under his leadership all staff are so friendly and approachable and wonderful with the children. We are so appreciate of the care taken here to accommodate so many little people, wonderful books, toys, scooters, pool toys,not to forget the magnificent kid-friendly meals provided. Thank you one and all.</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2017-09-03T00:44:06.007+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Jenny H, Australia</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID21023060</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID21118791</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Ltd Maisonbulle</Name>
    <SDate>2017-08-11T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2017-08-28T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>P00017</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>This is the most amazing place I have ever been to. The staff are helpful warm heart, kind people who are always there if we needed something. The house is well taken care of and we have been all over the world and we are never been anywhere with such an amazing warm and carrying team, lovely and kind people. Simply a peace of heaven.</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2017-09-04T00:10:40.793+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Aisha A, Indonesia</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID21118790</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID21421542</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Edge Retreats</Name>
    <SDate>2017-12-27T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2018-01-03T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>P00017</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>We have come to the end of our week staying at the stunning Kaba Kaba Estate. I have to say with all honestly that this family holiday has been far and away the best one we have had, and our whole family (all of us) agree, from the service, to the food and catering, it is unbeatable. The lovely team, led by Rahmat, could not do more for us. Every requested was met with a smile, and they were always there but yet discreet. I can truly say I will be highly recommending Kaba Kaba Estate to everyone.It was our first visit to Bali, but it wont be our last. The beautiful Balinese culture and hospitality shown through every member of the staff, and the gorgeous of the estate made us feel we were in Paradise. With heartfelt thanks to you all.</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2018-01-14T22:23:06.073+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Samia S, United Kingdom</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID21421541</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID21454114</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Dolphins Property</Name>
    <SDate>2018-01-10T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2018-01-12T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>P00017</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>This villa not only a luxury, there are also such a cultured atmosphere. Thanks Rahmat and villa staff service for making us feel the warmth and happiness. Thanks also for chatting with us about the history of villa's antique and stories. We liked the food of the villa, super delicious! Every details here is why we love it here. After two nights, we are agreed that the owner of the villa had a great taste and personality, to make the villa so perfect. Love the villa and people here.</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2018-02-16T22:15:05.987+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Melody W, Indonesia</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID21454113</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID21778092</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Jacob Mcluskie</Name>
    <SDate>2018-04-22T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2018-04-28T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>P00017</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>I wanted take this opportunity to thank you and your team for wonderful week. It's a delight to see everyone smiling throughout the day. Nothing was ever too hard and done with smile. The service was as beautiful as the villa, myself and the guests have had an amazing experience, thanks to you.</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2018-05-21T10:33:38.403+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Jacob M, Australia</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID21778091</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
</REVIEWS>