<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<REVIEWS>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>1</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Staff</Name>
    <SDate>2012-11-19T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2012-11-19T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight><p>
	We loved everything about Villa Voyage &ndash; the architecture, floating tent beds, beach access, cliff-top walks, and amazing views. Our dinner was outstanding. We thoroughly enjoyed our morning snorkelling excursion on the villa&rsquo;s own <i>jukung</i> boat, accompanied by a tasty <i>antipasti</i> picnic served while drifting in the calm azure waters of Nusa Penida&rsquo;s Gamat Bay.</p>
</RHighlight>
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>Voyage</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments><p>This Robinson-Crusoe-meets-Roberto-Cavalli villa is sensational! Not usually prone to hyperbole, we consider it nigh on impossible not to be bowled over by the entire ‘barefoot luxury’ Villa Voyage experience. From the moment we caught sight of the dramatic sea vista beyond the living room, we were completely hooked. We lazed on sun loungers and beanbags by the pool, enjoyed siestas on the mezzanine bedroom balcony, and slumbered within the “I had a farm in Africa” tent bed, soothed by the pounding surf. The staff looked after us brilliantly, serving us a delicious breakfast every morning in the beachfront gazebo, and a three-course candle-lit dinner (tenderloin steak for him, sea bass for me) accompanied by the best chips in Bali! (Ingredients – which are charged to guests at cost plus a 30% shopping fee - are boated in from the mainland fresh every day, so we were asked to make our menu selection ideally 48 hours in advance).</p><p>This is a place that doesn’t do things by halves; all the design details have been painstakingly thought through, right down to the place mats and napkins (different for each meal – what perfection!). We loved the ‘voyage’ theme – the exotic travel books, the safari-style furniture. Every inch of the villa is a rich sensory pleasure, packed with surprises and with no part overlooked…like the antique daybed in the shadows of a sacred tree by the villa temple and the gate to the beach</p><p>We could have happily stayed put at the pool, so deeply relaxing is the Voyage experience! But the villa’s open-sided van, and <i>jukung</i> (outrigger) encouraged us out of our indolence, and we loved exploring the island – next time we’ll make a point of diving with the manta rays! We also dipped into the beach club next door for a tasty lunch, and strolled along the cliff tops – Dream Beach is only ten minutes away, and the restaurants of Mushroom Bay not much further.</p><p>Would we return to Villa Voyage? In a heartbeat! We felt so privileged to be among its first guests, and think that, once word gets out, this tropical island hideaway is going to get booked solid – by families and groups of friends.</p></ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise><p>
	It&rsquo;s hard to fault Villa Voyage. It&rsquo;s an adventure to get there, but that&rsquo;s part of the exhilaration &ndash; and it&rsquo;s far more fun (and often faster) than being stuck in traffic travelling to a villa in some congested parts of the mainland! As with many beaches in Bali, the bay has strong currents so it&rsquo;s unsafe for swimming; but the villa&rsquo;s beachside pool is so gorgeous, you&rsquo;re not going to care. And if kids tire of building sandcastles and exploring rock-pools at low tide, Dream Beach &ndash; safe for swimming but without lifeguard &ndash; is only a short walk away. Small kids would require close supervision inside the house as there&rsquo;s only canvas fabric woven between the spindles beneath the handrail on the mezzanine walkway&hellip; and it&rsquo;s quite a drop to the living room below.</p>
</RUnpleasantSurprise>
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>8.70</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>9</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>9</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>9</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>9</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>8</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>9</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>8</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>9</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>8</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>9</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2012-11-19T00:00:00+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Staff</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>1</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID12843189</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Ciaran Caulfield</Name>
    <SDate>2012-07-31T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2012-08-02T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>Voyage</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>An extraordinary seafront villa newly constructed on the tropical island of Nusa Lombongan a mere 30 minute speedboat trip from Bali. The 'Wow' factor is everywhere from the travelers Trunk theme of yesteryear to the stunning views and gorgeous appointments both inside and outside the villa. The beach is secluded and of powder white coral sand. The infinity overflow pool is semi saline and with a funky fiber optic light system for nighttime. Music can be listened to everywhere in the villa courtesy of a built in state of the art sound system. The staff are just amazing and will look after you from the moment you arrive with no fuss whatsoever. Food was scrumptious with plenty of variety. Ample room for all the family or five couples to relax and enjoy a very unique seaside break. We will be back !</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>8.50</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>10</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>9</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>10</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>8</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>8</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>7</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>7</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>9</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>8</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>9</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2012-09-07T11:07:54.14+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>CC, Ireland</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID12843188</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID13428052</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Lisa Allen</Name>
    <SDate>2012-10-15T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2012-10-17T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>Voyage</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>The Voyage is in a terrific beach location and the interior sports wonderful furniture, decor, and best of all outdoor bathrooms. The in-house chef prepares the best food while the cocktails on the terrace overlooking the beach and pool at sunset are to die fot.</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>10.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>10</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>10</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>10</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>10</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>10</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>10</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>10</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>10</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>10</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>10</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2012-10-24T12:36:03.387+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>AL, Australia</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID13428051</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID13839017</ReviewsID>
    <Name>renae knight</Name>
    <SDate>2012-11-27T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2012-11-29T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>Voyage</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>Felt like we were part of the rich and famous world, unbelievable.</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>10.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>10</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>10</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>10</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>10</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>10</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>10</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>10</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>10</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>10</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>10</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2012-12-18T17:40:45.317+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>renae knight, Australia</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID13839016</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID14192587</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Penny Fountain</Name>
    <SDate>2013-01-10T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2013-01-19T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>Voyage</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>We had an amazing holiday at Villa Voyage with our extended family (9 of us)in January.  It is a truly beautiful house in a breathtaking location.  By far, the most memorable part of our stay was the staff....wonderful in every way.  The food and service was outstanding and the personalities fabulous too!  We loved the tasteful, interesting decor and many,many interesting books to read. I do hope that we are able to return in the not  too distant future.
Penny Fountain and family.</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>9.20</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>10</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>9</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>9</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>9</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>9</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>9</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>9</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>9</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>10</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>9</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2013-01-23T10:33:28.78+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Penny Fountain, Australia</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID14192586</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID15007477</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Pania Fox none</Name>
    <SDate>2013-04-17T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2013-04-22T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>Voyage</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments />
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>9.70</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>10</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>10</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>10</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>10</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>10</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>9</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>9</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>9</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>10</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>10</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2013-04-29T11:25:14.487+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Pania Fox none, Australia</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID15007476</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID15439512</ReviewsID>
    <Name>David Ashton</Name>
    <SDate>2013-05-22T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2013-05-25T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>Voyage</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>A most delightful stay we will definitely return here if we come back to Bali.  Chef was fantastic, supported by most helpful staff. </ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>9.20</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>9</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>9</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>9</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>9</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>9</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>9</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>9</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>10</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>10</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>9</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2013-09-05T15:36:03.563+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>David A, Australia</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID15439511</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID18502833</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Zoe Mossman</Name>
    <SDate>2014-08-31T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2014-09-10T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>Voyage</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>It was everything we hoped for and more.  The villa of the Island.  The holiday was made by the wonderful staff and the fantastic Balinese food.  </ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>10.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>10</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>10</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>10</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>10</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>10</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>10</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>10</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>10</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>10</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>10</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2014-09-24T10:17:39.02+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Zoe M, United Kingdom</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID18502832</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID18791585</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Glenn Shearer</Name>
    <SDate>2015-01-12T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2015-01-19T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>Voyage</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>Villa Managers and Staff where amazing 10 out 10 plus, food was nothing short of brilliant.</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>9.50</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>10</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>10</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>9</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>9</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>10</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>9</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>9</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>9</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>10</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>10</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2015-01-26T10:13:49.443+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Glenn Shearer, Australia</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID18791584</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID18543020</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Keryn Curtis</Name>
    <SDate>2014-09-22T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2014-09-28T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>Voyage</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>Actually, this was the best 'relaxing holiday' I think I have ever had.  So glad we didn't go to mainland Bali this time.  We adored the low key pace and the lack of cars, traffic, shops, chaos.  The villa is divine.  For us (two families with older teenage children) it was perfect to have the separate bedrooms and bathrooms for everyone but we also really loved that there was one big internal living space.  We felt that we (eight in total) could all be there together yet doing different things.  We brought paints and did lots of painting and drawing; we played scrabble, read extensively, swam, had a yoga teacher come and do a class each morning by the pool; wrote epistles!  The snorkeling and swimming with manta rays was totally fabulous; all the staff were gorgeous and amazing.  We totally loved Kadek, Gabriel and Wayan who we got to know most. The food was outstanding.  We had three meals outside the villa (including one at the much feted Indiana Kananga) and we felt on all three occasions that, while it was nice to have the excursion, the food was better from Wayan's kitchen.  It really was a very special holiday and we vow to be back before too long!  Suggestions?  Put some bicycles (maybe four) in the house so guests can take short bike rides.  And make the menus more 'asian'.  Next time I would just ask Wayan to prepare Indonesian and other Asian food as he thought best. His Indonesian banquets were outstanding and we wondered why anyone would want anything else!  The other two things I would say is:  1) it would be good if it was really stressed that you need to have lots of IDR in cash. Like about 10 000 000 a week?  I think that was roughly what we spent for the eight of us for the week but we didn't have time to get enough cash on the mainland so we were struggling a bit trying to keep the float going and hoping the one ATM would give us enough to get to the end of the week. 2) you also need to emphasise the limitations imposed by the speedboat travel with the last boat leaving from Sanur at 5pm.  For anyone coming from Australia at least, none of the flights come in before early afternoon and with the new airport customs arrangements, you need to allow a good two hours to get out of the airport (they have GOT to fix that!).  We very nearly missed our boat, despite the flight having arrived at 2.30pm.  It would be prudent for people to spend a night or two on the mainland to reduce the stress of trying to make the last boat.  But none of that takes away from the amazing holiday.  Truly, we are torn between telling everyone we know about our little slice of heaven...or NOT telling anyone.  This is the real Bali and real relaxation.</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>9.50</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>10</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>10</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>10</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>10</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>8</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>9</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>9</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>9</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>10</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>10</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2014-10-14T14:08:56.193+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Keryn C, Australia</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID18543019</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID18865846</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Diane  James</Name>
    <SDate>2015-02-13T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2015-02-17T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>Voyage</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>Villa Voyage is in a reasonably secluded location away from the chaos of Bali.   It offers uninterrupted views, peace and tranquility.  The Viila bedrooms are spacious, clean and very comfortable and above all, homely.  The overall feeling of the Villa is comfortable luxury without complication or fuss.  Our every need was taken care of and the staff are, without question, one of the greatest assets of the Villa.  We really enjoyed our time at the Villa and left feeling refreshed and revitalised.  We would not hesitate to recommend the Villa to any travellers who are looking for somewhere to recharge their batteries.</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>8.70</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>9</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>10</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>10</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>8</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>9</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>8</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>7</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>9</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>10</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>7</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2015-03-09T09:19:48.95+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Diane  James, Australia</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID18865845</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID19216467</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Milda Ratkelyte</Name>
    <SDate>2015-07-26T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2015-07-27T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>Voyage</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>We had a wonderful stay at Villa Voyage. Villa Manager Kadek was extremely friendly and very helpful. He helped us to organise private sunset yoga session and scooters for our stay. He also told us about all the best spots to explore on the magical Island of Nusa Lembongan. The villa itself was stunning and tastefully decorated. Loved the pool overlooking the ocean. Thanks so much for an amazing stay!</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>10.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>10</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>10</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>10</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>10</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>10</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>10</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>10</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>10</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>10</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>10</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2015-11-03T10:48:26.89+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Milda R, Singapore</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID19216466</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID19439710</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Mark Cross</Name>
    <SDate>2015-11-03T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2015-11-08T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>Voyage</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>We enjoyed our stay at Villa Voyage.  The house is spectacular and the views from the pool area are amazing.  The house should likely be advertised as a 4 bedroom house with a "granny-flat" or "nanny-flat" located in the front of the property away from the actual house/pool area.</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>6.60</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>7</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>9</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>8</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>8</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>4</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>7</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>7</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>8</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>3</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>5</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2015-11-13T16:12:48.097+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Mark C, Australia</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID19439709</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID21735186</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Beluga  Beluga Reisen GmBH</Name>
    <SDate>2018-04-07T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2018-04-14T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>Voyage</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>The staff are friendly and helpful. The food is delicious. The chef is always asking for menu in advance to make sure our guests get there requests. Nice villa with beautiful ocean views. Enjoyed the pool deck with all members in the group with nice atmosphere.</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2018-05-12T10:50:37.397+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Cathia S, Germany</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID21735185</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID21585563</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Travel Serv Co. Ltd.-Shanghai Beijing Zanadu International</Name>
    <SDate>2018-02-18T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2018-02-21T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>Voyage</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>Great place for family. It was nice to sit in the pool with ocean view.</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2018-05-08T13:05:08.4+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Wei X, China</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID21585562</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID21643296</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Qian Lyu</Name>
    <SDate>2018-03-10T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2018-03-12T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>Voyage</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>The villa is huge. My mom may cook together with staff like this in my own home. </ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2018-05-12T10:48:40.43+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Qian L, China</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID21643295</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID21884674</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Jacqueline Greger</Name>
    <SDate>2018-06-01T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2018-06-04T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>Voyage</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>Thank you so much for a wonderful stay at villa voyage. We spent 8 days in Indonesia and 3 days in Lembongan, it was our favorite! The villa is beautiful, the food was so good, the staff was fantastic. We will be back.</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2018-06-26T13:20:35.007+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Jacqueline G, United States</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID21884673</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID21783033</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Gemma Moffatt</Name>
    <SDate>2018-04-25T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2018-04-30T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>Voyage</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>A little bit more expensive than Bali for items in Lembongan. Staff is friendly and chef is good - food tastes delicious.</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2018-05-12T10:52:05.727+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Gemma M, Singapore</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID21783032</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID21988815</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Of Villas Ministry</Name>
    <SDate>2018-06-27T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2018-07-03T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>Voyage</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>Thanks so much to the whole team at Villa Voyage for making our stay at Lembongan so memorable. We really have a wonderful time with you all. We look forward to returning in the future. </ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2018-07-11T15:43:26.297+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Rebecca H, Australia</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID21988814</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID22264329</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Matt Annesley</Name>
    <SDate>2018-09-28T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2018-10-01T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>Voyage</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>Absolutely loved my stay at Villa Voyage, such as a beautiful place. Amazing staff and breath taking views, will definitely be coming back with friends from UK.</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2018-11-29T17:39:05.657+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Matt A, Australia</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID22264328</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID22115704</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Petrana Lorenz</Name>
    <SDate>2018-08-04T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2018-08-10T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>Voyage</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>As 3 families celebrating their 10 years wedding anniversary we were looking for something truly special and we found it. Thank you so much for helping us create such wonderful memories. This is a magical place, will never never forget and the kindness off the staff who made it such a pleasure each and every day.</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2018-10-10T17:03:23.353+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Petrana L, Australia</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID22115703</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID22137952</ReviewsID>
    <Name>C Asia Pte., Ltd Villa-Finder.com</Name>
    <SDate>2018-08-14T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2018-08-18T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>Voyage</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>We came from France, we see you beautiful country.  After Bali we had a very very happy in Lembongan. Many thanks to Hendra, Vian, Jeri for your hospitality and service. This island is wonderful, we hope we come again.</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2018-11-19T11:18:39.557+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Helene B, France</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID22137951</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID22011841</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Nusa Lembongan Villas</Name>
    <SDate>2018-07-04T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2018-07-11T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>Voyage</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>To all the staff at Villa Voyage - thank you so much for a truly wonderful stay at this lovely villa. You made us feel very welcome and looked after us so beautifully. We love your island of Nusa Lembongan.</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2018-10-09T16:03:19.717+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Andrea M, Indonesia</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID22011840</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID22150123</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Gigliola Maule</Name>
    <SDate>2018-08-19T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2018-08-22T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>Voyage</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>Beautiful experience in Villa Voyage, we discovered a magic place after many years traveling around Bali. Great atmosphere, excellent Staff, good vibes villa full of positive energies. We will be back.</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2018-11-19T11:59:25.227+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Gigliola M, Italy</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID22150122</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID22245298</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Of Villas Ministry</Name>
    <SDate>2018-09-21T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2018-09-24T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>Voyage</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>Seeing the view for the first time as we came up the stairs set us up for a truly amazing time on your island. Thanks to all staff who were always helpful and cooked us an incredible barbie on the deck. </ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2018-11-28T19:31:41.93+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Tim D, Australia</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID22245297</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID22071002</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Getaways Villa</Name>
    <SDate>2018-07-28T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2018-07-31T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>Voyage</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>Beautiful place to stay with lovely staff and island.</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2018-08-01T00:00:00+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Matthieu H, Australia</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID22071001</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID22187033</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Donny Basuki</Name>
    <SDate>2018-09-01T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2018-09-04T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>Voyage</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>A great experience voyage villa. Amazing location of course but the staff service makes all the difference, thank you.</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2018-11-19T20:38:58.553+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Donny B, Indonesia</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID22187032</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
</REVIEWS>