<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<REVIEWS>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>1</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Staff</Name>
    <SDate>2018-10-24T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2018-10-24T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight>So many Bali villas boast a private chef that it’s easy to become blasé. However Chef Adi ‘s meals are among the best we’ve enjoyed in any Bali villa… and his beautifully presented desserts are sublime. We were also very impressed with the spa therapists. For the staff alone we would return in a heartbeat.<br /></RHighlight>
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>P00233</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>Wow. Wow. WOWWWWWWW. Villa 1880 took my breath away the moment I arrived — no mean feat for a seasoned and perhaps super-critical reviewer of luxury villas. What exquisite taste the owners must possess, to have created such an appealing vacation home … and filled it with such covetable furniture and curios.&nbsp; This is surely a dream villa for anyone who appreciates inspiring design.<br /><br />We loved the unique blend of old and new — how the 138-year old plantation house sat so comfortably (and seamlessly) between the contemporary buildings. And I admit swooning over the uber-photogenic interiors filled with achingly chic designer furniture sitting on extraordinary brass inlaid flooring. The media room was fabulously flamboyant with sprawl-inducive sofas covered in pink velvet, a cocktail cabinet …and whatever prompted them to think of a stuffed peacock?&nbsp; Magic was in every detail — for example, our welcome drink was served in a hollowed-out pineapple, complete with bamboo straw, and breakfast included home-made strawberry jam, marmalade, and passion fruit preserve. And how sweet that half of the vanity in the kids’ bunkroom bathroom was set lower so little ones could reach the basin! (Though we were kid-free on our visit, we could imagine them cavorting around in the bunk room with glee). <br /><br />But what made our experience truly special was the staff. On a tropical island awash with villas boasting well-trained staff, Villa 1880’s raises the bar. Gede the manager was so charming and helpful – and the same went for the butlers we met… even the gardener was chatty. And we cannot enthuse enough about Chef Adi — a rare find, passionate about food and with an inventive mind. The meals we had at Villa 1880 were absolutely superb — oh for another of his home-made panacottas! Ria the spa therapist was also excellent, with a decade working at Shiva Som in the Maldives….whatever you do, don’t leave without having at least one massage with her in the villa’s beautiful spa room.<br /><br /></ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise>In a villa that exudes designer chic in every detail, the brass door handle to my bedroom proved a challenge for me — gorgeous to look at, but a tad stiff. Other than this almost comically tiny issue, and as hard as I tried to find flaws, Villa 1880 is faultless. <br /></RUnpleasantSurprise>
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>8.80</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>9</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>8</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>8</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>9</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>9</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>9</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>9</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>9</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>9</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>9</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2018-10-24T00:00:00+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Staff</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>1</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID22054129</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Acquired bookings Acquired bookings</Name>
    <SDate>2018-07-15T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2018-07-25T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>P00233</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>Thank you for wonderful stay in your Villa! It was perfect for our group, and very comfortable. We are lucky to have called it home for last ten days. The staff were exception, especially Widya and Putu. Nanik was lovely, and the chef was a fantastic cook. All our meals were excellent and the kids were very happy with the pancakes and fruit, and they loved the pasta and burgers. The adult dinners were delicious and varied. The staff learn your names (and coffee preferences) early and truly made us feel at home. The villa itself is gorgeous, we loved the unique design of old building. The kids bedroom, lounge room and table tennis areas were fantastic and well used. Comfortable beds. We loved Villa 1880 and would definitely recommend it. Thank you all so very, very much!</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2018-09-20T17:29:40.553+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Phil G, Australia</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID22054128</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID22107177</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Acquired bookings Acquired bookings</Name>
    <SDate>2018-08-02T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2018-08-08T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>P00233</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>Villa 1880 exceeded our expectation. The villa is excellent and extremely spacious. All the staff were so polite and were an extremely special part of our stay. We look forward to returning.</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2018-08-09T00:00:00+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Christine L, Australia</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID22107176</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID22146419</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Acquired bookings Acquired bookings</Name>
    <SDate>2018-08-17T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2018-08-21T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>P00233</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>The villa was amazing, good enough space for kids. The pool was good and we might be back very soon.</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2018-11-19T11:54:04.93+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Fajar, Australia</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID22146418</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID22187916</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Acquired bookings Acquired bookings</Name>
    <SDate>2018-08-08T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2018-08-15T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>p00233</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>Villa 1880 is absolute paradise, better than we could could have hoped for. The villa staff were so friendly and we all love them. We are going to miss the villa so much and hope one day we might be back. We absolutely loved Villa 1880 and did not want to leave! The beautiful gardens, gorgeous decor and generous space were just perfect. The friendly and attentive staff were our favorite part. The kids loved the pool and the bunk beds and the extra touches like kids books and movies made life so easy. The villa was wonderful. Usually the reality is not as good as the photos but in this time reality was better! The staff were wonderful and greatly added to the enjoyment of our stay.</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2018-11-19T11:13:39.997+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Sarah F, Australia</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>VM1880</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID22273438</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Julias  International BV</Name>
    <SDate>2018-09-24T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2018-10-04T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>P00233</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>Beautiful villa, loved the eclectic design and layout. Great space for a party 10 plus. Best of all the staff. Gede, Widya, Putu and all the team are so welcoming. Nothing is a problem. Thank you Villa 1880 for a wonderful holiday.</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2018-10-05T00:00:00+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Kate M, Australia</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID22273437</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID22316785</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Acquired bookings Acquired bookings</Name>
    <SDate>2018-10-12T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2018-10-19T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>p00233</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>Thank you for a lovely time. The pool, bed, food and massage were lovely. Thank you very much to everyone for one of the most special holidays we have all ever had. A particular thanks to Widya, Putu and Gede who were the very best and made our stay so wonderful. The villa, staff and everything else made this so fabulous, we will all be back.</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2018-12-10T12:46:19.69+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Catherine H, Australia</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>VM1880</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID22470319</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Acquired bookings Acquired bookings</Name>
    <SDate>2018-12-09T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2018-12-14T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>p00233</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>Our 1st villa experience and definitely a great one. The staff were amazing and nothing was too much trouble for them. Special thank you to Gede, Widya, Putu, Chef, Security and the quite lady who helped to cleaning our rooms daily. Quality food and great hospitality. Villa 1880 is the best. I love the burger and swimming pool.</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2019-01-04T10:59:23.88+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Geraldine T, Singapore</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>VM1880</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
</REVIEWS>