<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<REVIEWS>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>1</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Staff</Name>
    <SDate>2017-12-14T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2017-12-14T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight>The wooden sala by the swimming pool is an ideal place to laze around and enjoy the superb views during the day with two daybeds right on the edge of the beach and pool.&nbsp; Two separate living areas mean children can be nearby while still enjoying their own entertainment options.&nbsp; The location is private and peaceful, but having other villas nearby creates opportunities for kids (and adults) to make new friends on the beach. <br /></RHighlight>
    <RSurroundArea>There's really nothing to draw you away from the pool and beach at Akuvara.&nbsp; A stroll along the sand provides a sense of the island's past and the local fishermen and coconut farmers generally go about their business as if you weren't there.&nbsp; There are a couple of local food stalls on the road that splits the peninsula, and on the north-facing beach you will find a few fishermen's shacks and small beach resorts.&nbsp; For variation, a day spent poolside at the Nikki Beach Club, sipping mojitos and snacking on haute cuisine while listening to the latest dance tunes spun by the resident DJ, makes a nice change. Adjacent to Akuvara, four magnificent villas sit right by the beach.&nbsp; The area surrounding the ferry jetty has a very municipal feel (although there is an ATM there), so unless you decide to hire a car to explore the island's busier locations (villa staff can arrange car hire and taxis), it's all about kicking back with satisfied sigh. &nbsp;<br /></RSurroundArea>
    <VillaID>Akuvara</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>Akuvara's contemporary design may not be to everyone's taste, but once you settle into the tropical lifestyle on offer you soon appreciate the beauty of keeping things simple.&nbsp; The clean open spaces suit the environment and technological enhancements like the music and movie hard drive in the living rooms give the villa a distinctive, modern feel. <br /><br />Initially, we felt the three lounge areas to be excessive, but with kids in tow the option of a separate entertainment room in the evenings definitely appeals, and the upper floor lounge adds a new dimension to sunset cocktails.&nbsp; &nbsp;<br /><br />The staff are courteous and try hard to meet every request.&nbsp; Despite the occasional language barrier they manage to run everything smoothly while remaining unobtrusive and the English-speaking manager ensures the villa runs smoothly and deals with things like tour bookings and restaurant recommendations. <br /><br />This part of Lipa Noi offers a nice balance between seclusion and diversion.&nbsp; You can happily spend days doing very little, but a short drive to the other side of the peninsular brings you to some decent resort restaurants, as well as the Nikki Beach Club, which is far more sophisticated a venue than you'd expect to find in such a secluded location.&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;<br /><br />In some ways Akuvara felt like two villas in one.&nbsp; The studio at the rear of the property feels like an independent unit, but would certainly be a useful addition for a full family gathering.&nbsp; The option to rent the villa without this fourth bedroom, however, makes Akuvara a great choice as a functional but comfortable family getaway.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;<br /><br />If there is such a thing as villa envy then staying at Akuvara may inspire it as the villas close-by are significantly larger and more opulent than this one - but come with a much higher price tag.&nbsp; Yet despite its compact design, Akuvara still boasts the full range of amenities required to provide a pleasant beachside escape.&nbsp; Between the pool and the beach you never want for daytime pleasures and lazing in the ocean-front sala with a cool drink and a book must surely rate as one of life's finer moments. &nbsp;<br /></ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise>The plot next door is empty and at times does seem to be something of a dumping ground for local fishermen although the villas make an effort to keep it clean.&nbsp;  The bedrooms are not huge and can seem a little ‘boxy’ but are ideal for those who like their privacy when on holiday, as they are all situated in their own pavilions and black out curtains guarantee peaceful sleep.</RUnpleasantSurprise>
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>7.10</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>6</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>9</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>8</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>7</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>7</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>6</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>6</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>8</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>7</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>7</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2017-12-14T00:00:00+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Staff</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>1</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID11898704</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Jhumur Baruah</Name>
    <SDate>2012-05-31T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2012-06-08T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>Akuvara</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>We just returned after spending 8 fabulous days at Koh Samui at Villa Akuvara and would like to thank you for meeting our expectations about the quality of the property and the service levels of the staff at the Villa . We loved every minute of our stay there and would like to point out that the SERVICE was of VERY HIGH STANDARDS and we Indians can be very fussy about services . They were at our beck and call and with a smile 24/7 and no matter what we asked for , it was done within no time . The Chef did keep whipping up meal after meal for us and we were very sad to leave and hope to be back with a bigger group soon as we were not able to do a few things due to the weather playing spoilsport . 

We really have nothing negative to say about our entire experience right from booking. However, if we wanna criticize, then the only thing we came up with is that there are no telephones in the rooms (even for room-room communication). We realized this only the times when it rained really heavily and was difficult for us to step out since the rooms were not connected. But this wasn't really that big of a deal.

looking fwd to renting villas through you for all our vacations in the future . !! 
</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>9.80</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>10</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>10</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>10</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>10</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>10</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>9</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>9</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>10</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>10</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>10</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2012-06-19T16:09:21.297+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Jhumur Baruah, India</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID11898703</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID21572465</ReviewsID>
    <Name> Airbnb (17.7)</Name>
    <SDate>2018-02-11T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2018-02-17T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>Akuvara</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>Service standard was excellent, food taste was quite suitable for Chinese. Location is just great, facing a smooth leveled beach, people can swim, canoe and fish here. If we have another chance visiting Koh Samui in the future, we will come back here.</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2018-02-23T11:16:41.277+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Li F, China</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID21572464</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID21618540</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Ms. Sandra</Name>
    <SDate>2018-02-23T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2018-03-02T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>akuvara</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>Thank you for the amazing time in Akuvara. The hospitality was absolutely wonderful. This is truly one of the most beautiful places in the world. This was the best vacation we have ever had and we really want to return someday. The tree swing made the gorgeous beach even more special. We cannot get over how delicious all the food was. I think the best chef in the world resides here. We will miss the food! Thank you for an unforgettable time.


</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2018-05-08T13:13:09.023+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Graham M, Philippines</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>OPOceane</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID21688230</ReviewsID>
    <Name> Duke Technology Co. Ltd</Name>
    <SDate>2018-03-22T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2018-03-27T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>Akuvara</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>Staff here work enthusiastically, meals served were very close to our taste - so we felt as comfortable as if at home and were very happy. Rooms face ocean so we enjoyed a great view. Very suitable for families with kids, as we could play on the beach, look for shells - always entertained. Peaceful surrounding. We will stay here again if we come back to Koh Samui.</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2018-05-16T11:34:02.073+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Danni T, China</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID21688229</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID21716245</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Acquired bookings Acquired bookings</Name>
    <SDate>2018-04-02T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2018-04-07T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>Akuvara</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>We had a wonderful stay in Koh Samui! Our first trip to Thailand. From the amazing food - thank you Max and our service - thanks to Joy, our families shared unforgettable memories together. Thank you for an incredible stay at Akuvara. We enjoyed every minute and are so sad to say goodbye to the amazing staff - Joy, Max, Dang, Ning, see you again!
</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2018-05-18T17:17:34.017+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Laura D, Philippines</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID21716244</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
</REVIEWS>