<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<REVIEWS>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>1</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Staff</Name>
    <SDate>2012-08-01T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2012-08-01T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight><p>
	The pool is the most obvious highlight. Thirty metres of blue-tiled bliss that draw the whole villa together and set the scene for holiday heaven. But that&#39;s not to say that the beach isn&#39;t worth visiting. Practically deserted, the powdery sand and gentle seas are a major plus and the views from the beachside hammock out to the five small Islands and mainland beyond inspire you to artistic pursuits. In terms of facilities, the bedrooms are worthy of a special mention because they&#39;re not only stylish, bit also eminently practical and enjoy almost total privacy without losing out on the villa&#39;s bigger picture. Quite a feat of design.</p>
</RHighlight>
    <RSurroundArea><p>
	There&#39;s really nothing to pull you away from the pool and beach in Lipa Noi. A stroll along the sand provides a sense of the island&#39;s past and the local fishermen and coconut farmers generally go about their business as if you weren&#39;t there. There are a couple of local food stalls on the road that splits the peninsula, and on the opposite side you will find a few fishermen&#39;s shacks and small beach resorts. Adjacent to Baan Puri are three or four more magnificent villas which will often mean kids find new friends to explore with. Beyond the villas is a larger unfinished development &ndash; The Place, which is sufficiently far away not to disturb. The area surrounding the ferry jetty has a very municipal feel (there is an ATM there though), so unless you decide to hire a car to explore the island&#39;s busier locations, it&#39;s all about kicking back with satisfied sigh. The villa staff can arrange car hire and taxis.</p>
</RSurroundArea>
    <VillaID>BaanPuri</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments><p>Our visit to Baan Puri involved two families and the kids had an absolute ball, which meant we did too. Water plays a major role at the villa, with ponds, waterfalls - that huge 30m pool - and the waters of the Gulf of Thailand a constant influence. A particular joy is that, despite the villa's opulence, it remains refreshingly simple and focuses on what matters most during a beach holiday: comfort, privacy and the opportunity to enjoy the location to the full.</p><p>The staff were an absolute delight with the villa manager taking the kids under her wing as only the Thai’s know how and a superb chef who could cater for all tastes.Every room is designed to keep you all but physically attached to the view and the options for outdoor enjoyment are countless. A particular pleasure was the large circular daybed on the terrace in front of the beachfront bedroom, reclining with a chilled drink, breathing in the breeze with the pool and ocean before you can only be described as sublime. Versatility is another advantage.</p><p>The sheer size of the property, combined with its sensitive design, mean Baan Puri can happily host several families. There's even a table tennis table, beach toys, a Kayak, bikes and DVDs to keep the kids entertained when not in the pool or on the beach. But the villa would also be perfect for a large gathering of friends or a special celebration. Who could resist a party on the lush beachside lawn? Of course, not even high-end residences escape the odd architectural over-indulgence, but at Baan Puri, the few there are add character rather than inconvenience. A cliché I know but the only real disappointment was leaving.</p></ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise><p>
	The unfinished development next door is a bit of an eyesore, but for the most part it&rsquo;s invisible from inside the villa grounds and there was no construction noise at the time of writing (March 2009 &ndash; or on our revisit in June 2012). The master bedrooms feature raised bath tubs right next to the pool, with sliding doors for alfresco ablutions: this may be little risqu&eacute; for some tastes, but certainly adds a sense of fun. Access to the beach from the pool is down just one side, which can be a little frustrating, but then swimming is always the more tempting way to travel. Some guests may also be disappointed that the two master bedrooms have no TV.</p>
</RUnpleasantSurprise>
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>8.40</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>9</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>9</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>9</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>7</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>8</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>9</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>8</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>8</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>9</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>8</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2012-08-01T00:00:00+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Staff</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>1</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
</REVIEWS>