<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<REVIEWS>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>1</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Staff</Name>
    <SDate>2017-09-13T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2017-09-13T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight>Sea, sand and sunsets – tropical perfection! Many highlights here at Roxo: professional and friendly service, stunning location, fabulous views, vibrant design. <br /></RHighlight>
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>P00021</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>Villa Roxo’s design has a modern edge, yet its ambiance is cheerful, relaxed, and feels just right for the tropical setting.&nbsp; It’s easy to settle in, slide open the heavy glass doors and let the sea breezes flow as generously as the champagne you’ll crack open to celebrate arriving at one of Thailand’s most beautiful, peaceful beaches.&nbsp; The staff are equally as cheerful, and the maid always seemed to magically arrive just when a glass needed filling or a towel sourced.&nbsp; Though families are welcome, the sophisticated Sava leans more towards groups of adults – more ‘hen party’ hang-out than nest for mother hens.&nbsp; We didn’t party during our stay (we had work to do!) but with the chef and the divine open layout, a barbecue poolside soiree is a must-do here.&nbsp; There’s very little to fault with this villa, though, if we really have to be picky, being in the second tier of the estate means it takes that extra few seconds to reach the beach, and views are partially blocked by the villas in the front row.&nbsp; Although there’s plenty of privacy here, and peace and quiet abound in large doses, Roxo is part of an estate so it lacks the feel of a total hideaway.&nbsp; While we loved the sunny days, our favourite time was the evening, just after sunset.&nbsp; Sipping a glass of wine while soaking our feet in the pool, gazing up at the sparkling night sky to the sound of the waves – ahh, those tranquil tropical nights are heavenly!<br /></ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise>So close, yet not quite there – though the soft sands of Natai can be reached in seconds, Villa Roxo is separated from the beach by a row of villas.&nbsp; One of the twin-bedded rooms lacks a sea view, though its large windows overlook a pleasant tropical landscape. <br /></RUnpleasantSurprise>
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>8.10</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>8</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>8</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>8</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>8</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>8</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>8</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>8</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>8</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>9</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>8</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2017-09-13T00:00:00+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Staff</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>1</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
</REVIEWS>