<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<REVIEWS>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>1</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Staff</Name>
    <SDate>2013-03-05T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2013-03-05T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight><p>
	We loved having access to a wonderful, clean and long beach for walks, kayaking and general beach activities. There&rsquo;s a taste of yesteryear Samui here, as fishermen quietly sort their nets under a tree on the beach, right outside the villa.</p>
</RHighlight>
    <RSurroundArea><p>
	Lipa Noi is located on the quieter west coast of Samui. A few kilometres to the north is the island&rsquo;s capital of Nathon, which would be your closest shopping area for groceries, other than a few small convenience stores closer by. Lipa Noi is home to a few resorts with their own restaurants: Big John Restaurant at the Lipa Lovely Resort, a short walk along the beach from the villa, is well known for its seafood. Nikki Beach hosts regular parties and events, and is famous for its &lsquo;Amazing Sunday Brunch&rsquo; with DJs or live entertainment and an all-you-can-eat buffet next to the pool and beach. There are a few temples in the area: particularly worth seeing is Wat Hin Lad on the outskirts on Nathon before entering Lipa Noi. Here you&rsquo;ll also find elephant trekking and a waterfall. Generally speaking, Lipa Noi is a quiet location, about 30-45 minutes to the busier parts of the island.</p>
</RSurroundArea>
    <VillaID>Tawantok2</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>We particularly enjoyed the sense of space at the Tawantok Beach Villas created by the open walkways, skylights and uncluttered décor. Big groups won’t feel as though they’re on top of each other as there’s more than enough space between the lounge area, abundant pool loungers, the dining <span style="font-style: italic;">sala</span>, and the master suite’s own private lounge.<br /><br />We experienced the villa as a family. The staff were most accommodating, and it’s obvious they love having children as guests. We enjoyed the villa’s outdoor activities including a paddle in the kayaks and a game of volleyball on the beach (there’s a net set up). The tennis court is private, shared only with neighbouring Tawantok Beach Villa 2, which means that’s there’s no long waiting list to play, and the staff can even arrange a tennis coach (advance notice required). We had a long walk on the beach to build up an appetite before dinner, and this highlighted the villa’s ideal location for those seeking peace and tranquillity, but without being completely isolated. The beach is clean, and as we walked along we passed local children swimming and playing in the sand, fishermen setting out their nets and even a sunset wedding – very popular on Lipa Noi Beach. There aren’t any troublesome beach vendors along here, but there are a few resorts and restaurants if you want to stop for a drink along the way. Even better, enjoy sun-downers, as we did, lounging by the villa pool, taking in Lipa Noi’s famous sunset.<br /><br />We chose our dinner from the villa’s suggestion menu and enjoyed both Thai and Western dishes – salad, pasta and a vegetarian red curry, followed by a fresh fruit platter. What a treat to come back to a perfectly prepared meal after a long walk and a sunset swim!<br /><br /></ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise><p>We didn’t find this a problem, but the only TVs at the villa are in the main lounge area and the master suite lounge, so those that enjoy watching TV in bed may be disappointed. But with such a beautiful beach and pool outside, there’s no need to spend time in front of the TV.</p><p><br /></p></RUnpleasantSurprise>
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>7.60</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>8</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>8</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>8</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>7</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>7</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>7</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>7</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>8</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>8</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>8</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2013-03-05T00:00:00+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Staff</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>1</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID21568539</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Dummy TA Dummy TA</Name>
    <SDate>2018-02-05T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2018-02-15T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>Tawantok2</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>Our family has been staying in Villa Tawantok from 5th to 15th of February 2018. We want to pass great regards and appreciation to villa staff, chef and villa manager for their kindness and attention, for very good service and lovely atmosphere. Thank you so much! We will be back! See you!</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2018-02-23T11:28:26.733+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Anastasia S, Russia</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID21568538</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID21589028</ReviewsID>
    <Name>WUHU MILLIONAIRE</Name>
    <SDate>2018-02-16T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2018-02-22T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>Tawantok2</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>So glad to meet you all, it’s been wonderful with you for the past few days, your service made my whole family very happy, please accept my sincere gratitude.</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2018-02-23T11:28:52.2+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Yuting M, China</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID21589027</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID21650198</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Hui Hoon Chua</Name>
    <SDate>2018-03-10T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2018-03-14T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>Tawantok2</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>Thank you for your exceptional hospitality. Everything was well taken care of. The kids especially love playing by the pool. The pristine beach just in front of the villa adds a touch of charm to the whole place. My family and I would definitely revisit when we return to Koh Samui. 
</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2018-05-16T11:11:10.287+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Hui Hoon C, Singapore</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID21650197</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>URID21684688</ReviewsID>
    <Name> Samuidenmar</Name>
    <SDate>2018-03-18T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2018-03-26T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight />
    <RSurroundArea />
    <VillaID>Tawantok2</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>It was a wonderful pastime and beautiful rest. Everything was just wonderful - sea, food, weather, recreation program. Special thanks to Miss Luck and her team- such wonderful, kind and sympathetic people. Thank you.
</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise />
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>1.00</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>1</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>1</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>1</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>1</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>1</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>1</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>1</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>1</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>1</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>1</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2018-05-13T16:59:44.347+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Burman A, Kazakhstan</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>URID21684687</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
</REVIEWS>