<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<REVIEWS>
  <REVIEW>
    <ReviewsID>1</ReviewsID>
    <Name>Staff</Name>
    <SDate>2017-09-07T00:00:00+08:00</SDate>
    <EDate>2017-09-07T00:00:00+08:00</EDate>
    <RHighlight>We loved opening up the 'disappearing' glass doors through the entire living area –&nbsp; a refreshing way to greet the morning. The staff and facilities are all first class; we were never left wanting for anything. The poolside sunbeds are swish and super-comfy.</RHighlight>
    <RSurroundArea><p>
	It&rsquo;s getting harder to find in Thailand, but here in the Natai Beach area the landscape remains rural and people lead a quiet, traditional way of life. The beach stretches along the coastline for five kilometres, with soft white sands that you&rsquo;ll have virtually to yourself. Even at the height of the season there are just a sprinkling of people on the beach, and absolutely no commercial activity, a refreshing change from the busy beaches of island neighbour Phuket. The rickety old pier that you can see from the villa is probably 100 or more years old, once a launching point for transporting tin (the main industry in the region before tourism). It&rsquo;s now more often used by couples on a romantic sunset stroll.</p>
<p>
	You can drive for miles along the road that runs parallel to the beach, and at one point you&rsquo;ll reach a public pier where, in the late afternoon, the locals come to relax while fruit and snack vendors set up their stalls. There&rsquo;s fine dining to be enjoyed at the Aleenta and a few other Natai Beach resorts, or the villa manager can direct you to some of the excellent local seafood restaurants where you&rsquo;ll get to sample some more authentic Thai flavours.</p>
<p>
	The nearest town is Kokkloy, about five kilometres away. It&rsquo;s a typical Thai town, lined with concrete shop-houses, that so far remains free of any tourist activity. Those of us seeking an escape from the modern world may find it hard to believe that the opening of a Tesco-Lotus store would be something to cheer about, but the air of excitement is palpable when entering the icy air-conditioned interior of Kokkloy&rsquo;s shiny new supermarket.</p>
<p>
	Those wishing to indulge in some golf, shopping or sightseeing can drive over the bridge to Phuket. It takes about an hour by car to reach the main resort areas and Phuket City. For diving and snorkelling, day trips to the Similan islands may be arranged, with boats launching from Khao Lak, about 45 kilometres to the north.</p>
</RSurroundArea>
    <VillaID>Sava7</VillaID>
    <ROverallComments>Fun and flashy, Villa Aqua has a fantastic ultramodern design, yet the ambiance is cheerful, relaxed, and feels just right for the tropical setting. It’s easy to settle in, whip open the heavy glass doors and let the sea breezes flow as generously as that champagne that you’ll crack open to celebrate arriving at one of Thailand’s most beautiful, peaceful beaches. The staff are equally as cheerful, and the maid always seemed to magically arrive just when a glass needed filling or a towel sourced. Though families are welcome, the sophisticated Sava leans more towards groups of adults –more 'hen party' hang-out than a mother hens' nest. We didn’t party during our stay (we had work to do!) but with the fabulous entertainment system, the chef and the divine open layout, a barbecue poolside soiree is a must-do here. We were told that all the holiday villas in this estate have played host to some great events and weddings, and the management company can liaise with local event planners to help with larger events needing more staff and services.<br /><br />There’s very little to fault with this villa, though, if we really have to be picky, being in the second tier of the estate means it takes that extra few seconds to reach the beach, and views are partially blocked by the villas in the front row. Although there’s plenty of privacy here, and peace and quiet abound in large doses, the villa is part of an estate so it lacks the feel of a total hideaway. While we loved the sunny days, our favourite time was the evening, just after sunset. Sipping a glass of wine while soaking our feet in the pool, gazing up at the sparkling night sky to the sound of the waves – ahh, those tranquil tropical nights are heavenly!</ROverallComments>
    <RUnpleasantSurprise>So close, yet not quite there – though the soft sands can be reached in seconds, Villa Aqua is separated from the beach by a row of villas. The twin-bedded room lacks a sea view, though its large windows overlook a pleasant tropical landscape.</RUnpleasantSurprise>
    <RRestShop />
    <ApprStatusID>Approved</ApprStatusID>
    <RAttraction />
    <RIOverAll>8.10</RIOverAll>
    <RICharacter>8</RICharacter>
    <RILocation>8</RILocation>
    <RIOutsideArea>8</RIOutsideArea>
    <RILivingArea>8</RILivingArea>
    <RIKitchen>8</RIKitchen>
    <RIBedRm>8</RIBedRm>
    <RIBathRm>8</RIBathRm>
    <RIFacility>9</RIFacility>
    <RIStaff>8</RIStaff>
    <RIValue>8</RIValue>
    <RIDate>2017-09-07T00:00:00+08:00</RIDate>
    <RStatusID>V</RStatusID>
    <ReviewByName>Staff</ReviewByName>
    <UserTaskID>1</UserTaskID>
  </REVIEW>
</REVIEWS>